// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who is the founder of C-programming language",
    answer: "Dennis Ritchie",
    options: [
      "Dennis Ritchie",
      "James Gosling",
      "Marting Richard",
      "Einstein"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "What is the size of `int`",
    answer: "Compiler Dependent",
    options: [
      "-2",
      "-4",
      "-8",
      "Compiler Dependent"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "In DOS, What is the purpose of the function randomize() in Turboc C?",
    answer: "Displays a random number generator with a random value based on time",
    options: [
      "Displays a random number generator with a random value based on time",
      "Displays a random number",
      "Displays a random number generator in the specified range",
      "Invalid function"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "To print a float value which format specifier can be used?",
    answer: "%f",
    options: [
      "%f",
      "%lf",
      "%Lf",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "The concept of two functions with same name is known as",
    answer: "Function Overloading",
    options: [
      "Operator Overloading",
      "Function Overloading",
      "Function Overriding",
      "Function renaming"
    ]
  },

    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "A single line comment in C language source code can begin with ",
    answer: "//",
    options: [
      ";",
      ":",
      "/*",
      "//"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "The C library function rewind() reposition the file pointer at the begining of the file",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "'Stderr' is a standard error",
    answer: "Standard error streams",
    options: [
      "Yes",
      "Standard error streams",
      "Standard error types",
      "Standad error function"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which among the following is NOT a logical or relational operator?",
    answer: "=",
    options: [
      "!=",
      "==",
      "||",
      "="
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "Default storage class if not any is specified for a local variable, is auto",
    answer: "True",
    options: [
      "True",
      "False"
    ]
  },

];